The Cursed Puppet
(いの)ねえ 巻物は揃ってるし➡
Hey, we have both scrolls,
so let's go straight for the goal.
一直線に ゴールしちゃおうよ。
(チョウジ)そうしたいけどね。
I wish we could,
待ち伏せを受ける
可能性が高いと➡
but there's a high risk of
getting ambushed.
やっぱりサクラの作戦どおり
迂回ルートで…。
We should stick to Sakura's plan
and take the detour.
(チョウジ)サクラ？
(いの)ん？
Sakura…?
(いの)あっ サクラ!?
Sakura!
(サクラ)ハァ ハァ ハァ。
サクラ。
Sakura…
ハァ ハァ…。
２つの… ダム。
Two dams…
((綱手 : これから教えるのは➡
Next, I'm going to teach you
the jutsu to revive all the organs,
すべての器官 組織を再生する術。
the entire system.
その名も忍法 創造再生。
It's called the Ninja Art:
Mitotic Regeneration Jutsu.
忍法 創造再生？
Ninja Art…
Mitotic Regeneration?
これは回復能力の術ではない。
This isn't a jutsu that revolves
around healing skills.
初代火影が使っていたのと同じ➡
It's the same kind of
regeneration jutsu
再生能力の術だ。
that the First Hokage used.
(綱手)初代は膨大なチャクラを
持っていたため➡
The First Hokage had
such enormous chakra that
印を結ぶことなく発動していた。
he could activate it
without weaving signs.
そんな大量のチャクラ
私にはありません。
I don't have
that kind of immense chakra.
そこで もう１つ教える術がある。
So…there's one more jutsu
I will teach you.
百豪の術だ。
It's called
The 100 Healings Jutsu.
百豪の術？
The 100 Healings Jutsu?
私にも初代ほどのチャクラはない。
Even I don't have the kind of chakra
that the First Hokage had.
そこで開発したのが この術だ。
So I developed this jutsu.
この術を使えば➡
By using it, you can keep
a huge amount of chakra in reserve.
大量のチャクラを
ためておくことができる。
(綱手)この２つを
併用することにより➡
By combining these two,
体は再生し続け
その間 死ぬことはなくなる。
the body will continue
to regenerate and
you will not die during that time.
(サクラ)す すごい。
A-Amazing…
(綱手)しかしな➡
However, there's a problem with
The 100 Healings Jutsu.
問題なのは百豪の術だ。
至極緻密なチャクラコントロールを
必要とするうえ➡
Not only does it require extremely
delicate chakra control,
３年間 一定のチャクラを➡
you must amass chakra
for three years.
ため続けなければならない。
(サクラ)３年も…。
Three years…?
(綱手)うむ 一定のチャクラが
練られているな。
You have a constant amount
of chakra infused.
その状態を３年間
維持するんだぞ。
Well, you must maintain
that state for three years!
くっ…。
100 HEALINGS
《この状態で３年間も…》
I have to maintain this condition
for three years?!
はぁ～！
あぁ…。
(綱手)サクラ！
Sakura!
ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
百豪の影響で ふだん使える➡
Due to the effect of
The 100 Healings Jutsu,
your normal chakra level
has become extremely low.
チャクラの量が
極端に少なくなっている。
これでは
治療や戦闘に支障をきたす。
This will only be a hindrance
during healing and in battle.
手術も前に出て戦うことも➡
At this rate, I can't allow you
to perform any surgery
許可することはできんぞ。
or go out into the battlefield.
百豪の術とは別に➡
The 100 Healings Jutsu creates
a smaller secondary dam
チャクラをためておくことができる➡
in which to store
the chakra reserve…
小さなダムを もう１つ作る。
２つのダムのチャクラを➡
If I keep two dams of chakra and
目的別に使い分ければ➡
make sure I use each of them
for their specific purpose…
手術も前に出て戦うことも➡
I should be able to perform surgery
as well as fight in battles!
(可能になるはず))
あっ！
いの チョウジ！ 敵？
Ino! Choji!
Is it an enemy?
(サクラ)人形!?
A doll?
(サヤ)ウフフフッ ほんとにいい子ですわ。
You're such a good girl…
(サヤ)獲物を見つけてくれるなんて。
…for finding me some prey.
サクラ 体のほうは大丈夫？
Sakura, are you holding up physically?
うん 休ませてもらったから。
Yes, since you let me rest…
(サナ)お姉様 さっさと
殺しちゃいましょうよ。
Elder Sister,
let's hurry and kill them.
(マムシ)そんなに焦んなよ。
サヤお嬢が怒るぜ。
Don't be so hasty, Sana.
You'll get Saya mad.
お姉様だって➡
I'm sure Elder Sister wants to
get this over with quickly too.
とっとと片づけたいに
決まってるじゃない。
(サナ)ねぇ お姉様。
Right, Elder Sister…?
ヘヘヘヘッ！ ならば… うおっ。
All right then…
Saya, damn you…!
サヤ てめえ！ ひいっ。
サヤ… お嬢様。
L-Lady Saya!
私のお人形が見つけた獲物➡
I shall take my time…
じっくり呪ってさしあげる
ことにしますわ。
and curse these victims
that my doll has found.
じゃ じゃあ
どいつからやるんだよ！
Th-Then which one
will we kill first?
ですか…。
そうね➡
Let's see…
ウフフフッ ２人とも
とってもかわいいのですわ。
They are both quite cute…
They will be worth killing.
やりがいがありそう。
う～ん デブはいらない。
I don't want the fatso…
Fatso!
デブ！ てめえは俺の獲物だ！
You're mine!
僕は… ぽっちゃり系だ！
I…am…
pleasingly plump!
Put it any way you like.
A fatso's still a fatso!
言い方 変えても デブはデブだ！
グヘヘヘッ！
こいつ… やばい。
チョウジ！
This guy's dangerous!
Choji!
じゃあ 私は金髪を。
あの子は私の。
Then I'll take the blonde one.
She is mine.
じゃあ おでこを。
あれも私の。
Then one with
the big forehead…
She is mine as well.
デブ！
Fatso!
(チョウジ)ぽっちゃり系だって～の！
I said I'm pleasingly plump!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
部分倍化の術！
グヘヘッ 危なかったぜ。
That was close!
チョウジ！
Choji!
あいつ… 傀儡使い！
She's…a Puppet User!
あなたは呪われた。
You have been cursed.
もう この子から逃げられない。
You can no longer…
escape from her.
If she's the Puppet User,
《相手が傀儡使いなら
術者さえやれば…》
as long as we bring down
the jutsu caster…
サクラ 私の体を。
Sakura, my body…!
任せて。
Leave it to me!
Mind…!
心転身の…。
傀儡もどきの術。
Puppet Imitation Jutsu.
いの？
Ino…?
いの!?
Ino?!
(チョウジ)うわぁ！
チョウジ！
Choji!
《私がやるしかない… でも》
It's up to me to do this…
But…
いの！ サクラ！
Ino! Sakura!
仲間を心配してる場合じゃねえぞ。
This is not the time to worry
about your friends.
あなたも大ピンチなのよ。 フフフフッ。
You're in quite a bind too, you know.
超倍化の術！
Super Expansion Jutsu!
食べちゃうぞ～。
I'll eat you!
いの！
Ino!
な 何なの？
W-What is it?
傀儡もどきの術。
Puppet Imitation Jutsu!
術にかけられて わかったわ。
I realized it after I was
under that jutsu.
呪いとかいうのは
傀儡の術なんかじゃない。
She calls it a curse,
but it's not a Puppet Jutsu.
心転身の術に近いものよ。
It's closer to
a Mind Transfer Jutsu.
ああ～！
山中一族の面目丸つぶれ！
Aw man!
The Yamanaka Clan's reputation
is ruined!
(サナ)お姉様 助かりましたわ！
Elder Sister, thanks for
coming to my rescue!
(マムシ)サヤお嬢 あいつらを
叩きのめしてくれ！
Lady Saya!
Curse those guys!
言われるまでもない。
容赦しませんわ。
– There's no need to tell me that.
– I shall show no mercy.
この人形は 私のもの。
This doll is mine…
さぁ おいき！
Now, go!
Punish your arrogant friends!
生意気なお友達に
お仕置きをしておあげ！
(サクラ)い… いの こっち来るわよ。
I-Ino, he's coming this way!
(いの)こうなったら
やっぱり 術者を…。
Then there's only one way.
We have to get the jutsu caster…
いの？
Ino…?
山中一族が 心転身で
負けるわけにはいかないのよ！
No one beats the Yamanaka Clan
in Mind Transfer!
心転身の術！
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
(いの)チョウジ！
あら？
Choji!
Oh?
ダメじゃない
私のお人形さんの中に➡
That's not nice.
You can't enter my doll
without permission…
勝手に入ってきちゃ。
出てって。
Get out!
チョウジは 私たちの仲間よ！
Choji is our friend!
So you get out!
あんたこそ出てって！
フン…。
((これでは 手術も
前に出て戦うことも➡
At this rate, I can't allow you
to perform any surgery
or go out into the battlefront.
(許可することはできんぞ！))
くっ…。
《サクラ : まだだ… まだ チャクラが…》
I need much…much more chakra…
I need much…more chakra…
《あの頃の私は ただ
いつも２人に守られて➡
Back then, I was…
always being protected by those two…
その後ろ姿を見ていただけ。
and watching from behind.
でも もう あの時とは違う。
But times have changed.
チャクラさえあれば 戦える！》
If I have chakra, I can fight.
(大蛇丸)見事なものね。
Isn't that magnificent?
順調に仕上がっている
ということかしら。
I guess you're just about ready.
(サスケ)まだだ。
イタチを倒すには もっと力がいる。
Not yet.
I need more power in order
to take down Itachi.
(カブト)大蛇丸様。
Lord Orochimaru!
先ほど 例の試薬が完成しました。
The aforementioned reagent
has just been completed.
(大蛇丸)そう 水月に使うやつね？
Oh…
The one to test on Suigetsu?
実験担当は？
(カブト)香燐にやらせます。
Who is overseeing the experiment?
I'll have Karin do it.
２人は 今 東アジトだったかしら？
Aren't they both in
the east hideout?
ええ すぐに部下に運ばせます。
Yes, I'm dispatching
a subordinate right away to bring them.
俺が運んでやる。
I'll go get them.
あら どういう風の吹き回し？
Oh?
What brought this on?
フン… ただの暇つぶしだ。
I'm bored, that's all.
(香燐)珍しいこともあるもんだな。
お前が来るなんて。
Wonders never cease.
I can't believe you're here.
気にするな。
Don't worry.
用が済んだら すぐ帰る。
I'm leaving the minute
I'm done here.
べべ 別に気にしてないし！
I-I'm not worried!
ってか
クスリ 届くの遅すぎだろ。
Anyway, you're late bringing
the medicine!
(水月)あ～あ キミが大蛇丸の
パシリだなんてがっかりだよ。
I'm so disappointed that
Orochimaru's lackey is you.
(水月)まさか こいつみたいに➡
I sure hope you don't plan
大蛇丸の ペットに
なり下がる気じゃないだろうね。
on becoming Orochimaru's pet
like this one.
誰がペットだ こら！
Who did you call a pet?!
うちは 実験の準備にかかる。
I'm going to get ready
for the experiment.
サスケ お前もこんなやつ
相手にするな。
Sasuke, don't bother with this guy!
(水月)サスケ マジで助けてくんない？
Sasuke, seriously…
Will you help me?
こんな場所 もううんざりだ。
I'm sick and tired of this place.
それは お前の力次第だ。
That all depends on your strength.
(水月)チェッ。
Sheesh…
おい。
えっ。
Hey…
あ…。
やれやれ どんなえぐい実験が
始まるのやら…。
Aw man, what kind of horrible experiment
is it gonna be this time?
あ～。
おい お前！
Hey, you…!
バカ！ 何やってんだ！
ラッキー！
You fool, what are you doing?!
Lucky me!
(香燐)水月を逃がしただと!?
You let Suigetsu escape…?!
自分が気がついたときには
このありさまで…。
When I came to,
everything was like this.
クソ！ こんなことがバレたら➡
Damn it!
If Lord Orochimaru finds out
about this, he'll take it out on me!
大蛇丸様に
むちゃくちゃ怒られる！
すぐに追うぞ！
みんなを集めてこい！
We're going after him now!
Round up everyone!
はっ！
それで何とかなる相手なのか？
And what good will
that do against him?
サスケ お前 まだいたのか？
Sasuke! You're still here?!
実験を見ていくのも
悪くないかと思ってな。
I figured it might be interesting
to watch the experiment.
それより どうする？
どうするって…。
Anyway, what will you do?
Do...?
ついでだ
お前に手を貸してやる。
Since I'm here,
I'll lend you a hand.
あっちだ！
Over that way…
１時の方向！
感知能力か。
Towards 1 o'clock!
Sensory Perception?
ああ 知ってる相手なら
離れていてもチャクラを追える。
Yeah, if it's someone I know,
I can go after their chakra.
便利だな だが腑に落ちない。
That's convenient.
But I don't get it.
それほどの力があれば➡
With that kind of power,
大蛇丸から
逃げられそうなものだが。
I'd think you could get away
from Orochimaru.
なぜって…。
That's because…
((あぁ～！ 助けて！
Help!
この赤い髪 うずしおの生き残りに
間違いなさそうだ。
I'll bet this redhead
is a remnant
of a clan from the Hidden Eddies…
小遣い稼ぎに寄って
正解だったな。
You were right that
she'd be worth something.
離して！ 離してよ！
Let me go! Let me go!
往生際の悪いガキだぜ。
She's a pretty feisty kid.
お前ら 珍しい力を
持ってるんだってな。
I hear you have an unusual power.
そういう忍は
地下で高く売れるんだよ。
We'll get a good price
for you underground.
ヘヘヘ…。
(大蛇丸)故郷をなくした
忍っていうのは➡
A shinobi without a homeland
哀れなものね。 どこかの里に
身をよせたところで➡
is quite tragic.
No matter where you end up,
you're treated like a outcast.
しょせん 異端者扱い。
おまけに 特殊体質ともなれば
どこへ行っても狙われる。
And if you possess attributes
that are unusual,
they come after you…
as long as you're living.
生きてる限りずっと。
まあ そういう私も
狙う側なんだけど フフフ…。
Well… I speak as
one of the hunted too.
でもね
どうせなら自分で決めなさい。
But, you know…
You must decide for yourself.
(私のもとに来れば もう誰も
あなたに手は出せないわ))
If you come with me,
no one will ever touch you again.
どうせ従うなら
力のあるやつがいい。
If I have to follow someone…
I'd rather it be someone strong.
つまり 大蛇丸より
俺が強ければ➡
So if I'm stronger than Orochimaru,
you'd follow me?
乗りかえる気はあるってことか。
(香燐)チッ！ 川か やっかいだな。
Damn, a river…
What a nuisance.
気をつけろよ サスケ。
Watch out, Sasuke.
姿はないが やつはここにいる。
We may not see him, but he's here.
ああ。
Yeah.
やっぱり 騙し討ちには
やられないか。
I guess I can't fool you.
でも キミまで
追いかけて来るとはね。
But…
I didn't expect you
to be with her.
サスケは 大蛇丸様のもとにいるんだ。
Sasuke follows Lord Orochimaru!
What did you expect?!
当然だろ。
キミは黙ってよ。
You be quiet.
ねえ サスケ どうせなら➡
Hey, Sasuke…
If you're willing to follow her,
why not come with me instead?
あの女じゃなくて 僕につかない？
はあ!? 何言ってんだよ お前！
Huh?! What're you saying, idiot?!
キミとやり合う理由はないんだしさ。
I have no reason to argue with you.
無視すんな！
Don't ignore me!
I already answered that question.
その答えなら もう伝えたはずだ。
Oh yeah… you did say it
all depends on my strength?
そういえば 僕の力次第って
言ってたっけ？
水分身！
A Water Clone!
そいつに
物理攻撃は効かない！ 雷遁を！
Physical attacks don't work on him!
Use Lightning Style…!
印なんか結ばせないよっ！
I won't let you weave any signs…
(香燐)サスケ！
Sasuke!
ごめんね サスケ君。
I'm so sorry, Sasuke…
なんちゃって。
へえ～ いい刀だね。
Just kidding!
Hey, that's a nice blade.
Well then…
さ～て 次はキミの番だよ。
You're next…
おとなしく一緒に戻れ。
Just obey and return with me.
Or you'll regret it.
じゃないと 後悔することになる。
何それ。 脅しのつもり？
What? Is that a threat?
なんだよ 今の…。
What was that just now?
さすがに お前にも効いただろ…。
As expected…
It even worked on you.
《この鎖は
チャクラの塊だって縛れるって➡
Lord Orochimaru said…
that this chain can even bind
a mass of chakra.
大蛇丸様は言ってたけど…。
まだ 自在に使うとこまでは…》
But I had never used it before.
もういい。 香燐 それをしまえ。
That's enough, Karin.
Put that away.
あれ？ サスケ…。
Huh? Sasuke…
しまうんだ。
Put it away.
《この２人
いずれは俺の仲間にする。
In time, I'll get these two
on my side.
それだけの力を持っている》
Their powers will be worth it.
Ino's Mind Transfer failed?
《いのの心転身が負けた!?》
《まだ… チャクラが！》
Not yet…I don't have
enough chakra yet…
Choji and Ino are using up
their chakra
due to all these successive battles.
Their strength and willpower
are at their limits!
Back then, all I ever did
皆さん こんばんは。
前川清です。
was have Sasuke and Naruto
protect me.
今 私たちは
東京の有楽町に来ております。
Now, I should be able
to protect them…
夜になりますと
この有楽町 家路に急ぐ方➡
あるいは 一杯飲みに行く方
いらっしゃいますよね。
いろんな思いの方が たくさん
いらっしゃるんでしょうね。
今回の 「モクハチ」は
有楽町にあります➡
東京国際フォーラムより
２時間スペシャルをお送りいたします。